http://www.godandscience.org/privacy.html

Evidence for God from Science: Christian Apologetics
Privacy Statement for Evidence for God from Science
General Privacy Policies
Evidence for God from Science does not release any kind of personal
information collected from the website to any entity outside our organization.
This information includes, but is not limited to e-mail addresses,
correspondence, and site statistics. Writing to the ministry will not add your
name, e-mail, or any other personal information to any list (including our own).
You must specifically request to be added to any lists. Now here is the legal/technical
stuff:
About Us
This is a privacy policy for Evidence for God from Science.
Our homepage on the Web is located at
http://www.godandscience.org.
The full text of our privacy policy is available on the Web at
http://www.godandscience.org/privacy.html.
Users may go to
http://www.godandscience.org/privacy.html for information on how to opt-in or opt-out of use of their information.
We invite you to contact us if you have questions about this policy.
You may contact us by mail at the following address:
You may contact us by e-mail by clicking
here.
You may contact us by telephone at (626) 87-BIBLE [(626) 872-4253].
Dispute Resolution and Privacy Seals
We have the following privacy seals and/or dispute resolution mechanisms.
If you think we have not followed our privacy policy in some way, they can help you resolve your concern.
Disputes:
Errors or wrongful actions arising in connection with the privacy policy will be corrected by our organization.
Additional Information
This policy is valid for 1 day from the time that it is loaded by a client.
Data Collection
P3P policies declare the data they collect in groups (also referred to as "statements").
This policy contains 3 data groups.
The data practices of each group will be explained separately.
Group "Basic information"
We collect the following information:
Click-stream data
HTTP protocol elements
Search terms
This data will be used for the following purposes:
Completion and support of the current activity.
Web site and system administration.
Research and development.
This data will be used by ourselves and our agents.
The following explanation is provided for why this data is collected:
Data collected from all Web users:
access logs, and search strings (if
entered).
Group "Cookies"
We collect the following information:
HTTP cookies
This data will be used for the following purposes:
Completion and support of the current activity.
One-time tailoring.
This data will be used by ourselves and our agents.
The data in this group has been marked as non-identifiable. This means that there is no
reasonable way for the site to identify the individual person this data was collected from.
The following explanation is provided for why this data is collected:
Cookies are used to track visitors to
our site, so we can better understand
what portions of our site best serve
you.
Group "Mailing registration"
At the user's option, we will collect the following data:
Online contact information
Preference data
This data will be used for the following purposes:
Completion and support of the current activity.
Contacting visitors for marketing of services or products. The user must opt-in to this usage.
This data will be used by ourselves and our agents.
The following explanation is provided for why this data is collected:
This information is collected so that
we can send you valuable and useful
information which is relevant to your
needs and interests.
Cookies
Cookies are a technology which can be used to provide you with tailored information from a Web site. A cookie is an element of data that a Web site can send to your browser, which may then store it on your system. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it.
Our site makes use of cookies.
Cookies are used for the following purposes:
Completing the user's current activity
User targeting
Compact Policy Summary
The compact policy which corresponds to this privacy policy is:
CP="CAO DSP COR CURa ADMa DEVa TAIa CONi OUR IND ONL
UNI COM NAV INT PRE"
The following table explains the meaning of each field in the compact policy.
Compact Policy
Field
Meaning
CP=
This is the compact policy header; it indicates that what follows is a P3P compact policy.
CAO
Access is available to contact and other information.
DSP
The policy contains at least one dispute-resolution mechanism.
COR
Violations of this policy will be corrected.
CURa
The data is used for completion of the current activity.
ADMa
The data is used for site administration.
DEVa
The data is used for research and development.
TAIa
The data is used for tailoring the site.
CONi
The data is used for contacting the user, if the user selects it.
OUR
The data is given to ourselves and our agents.
IND
The data will be kept indefinitely.
ONL
Online contact information is collected.
UNI
Unique identifiers are collected.
COM
Computer information is collected.
NAV
Navigation and clickstream data is collected.
INT
Interactive data is collected.
PRE
Preference information is collected.
http://www.godandscience.org/privacy.htmlLast Modified February 20, 2012
Help I can't see!
Beliefs (more)
Christians & Santa Claus?
God's Crime Scene
God of the Big Bang
The Proverbs 31 Woman
A Young Earth Anthropology Paradox
UFO-Demon Connection (YouTube)
UFOs Part 1 (YouTube)
Critique of Young-Earth Creationism
Weird, Non-carbon Life?
UFOs and Demons
Peppered Moth (YouTube)
Ontogeny 	Recapitulates Phylogeny (YouTube)
The fool says "There is no God."
Banana-Eating Moth Evolution?
Designs in DNA (YouTube)
Who Was Noah?
God Punishes Children for Fathers?
Lunar Craters & Young Earth
Many Called, Few Chosen
Genetically Modified Food?
Genesis & Age of the Earth
Adam's Sin Changed Creation?
Nostradamus Predictions
Something Instead of Nothing?
The Trinity
Who is Jesus Christ?
Who is God?
What Is Christianity?
Was Jesus God?
Singularity Movement
Stephen Hawking & God
Who is Satan?
Medical Marijuana 'Benefits'
Natural Evil
Why are Scientists Atheists?
God of the Gaps
Who Created God?
Living Together a Good Idea?
